Second bout. On the east side, Tsuji-kun.
（アナウンス）
二陣戦 東 辻(つじ)君　西 澤井(さわい)君
On the west side, Sawai-kun.
（男性１）えっ？　誰？
Huh? Who's that?
He was sitting where
the trainer usually sits.
（男性２）
確か 監督席に座ってたヤツだよな
（男性１）
へえ…　あいつも選手だったのか
So he's a sumo wrestler, too?
（礼奈(れいな)）ダチ高 ファイトー！
Dachi High, fight!
（蛍(けい)）すみませんでした 監督
I'm sorry, Coach.
I tried a move we hadn't
discussed beforehand.
立ち合い 指示にないことを
勝手に やったりして
And this was the result.
あげく このザマです
I'm the one who should apologize.
（桐仁(きりひと)）謝らなきゃいけねえのは
俺のほうだよ
（桐仁）お前は 俺が
求める以上のことを やってのけた
You did what I asked and then some.
The fact that you still lost...
それでも勝てなかったのは
俺の力が足りなかったからだ
is a failure on my part.
“全国で お前を勝たせる”
I couldn't keep the promise I made to you
about getting you a win at Nationals.
その約束を
果たすことができなかった
I'm truly sorry.
ホントに すまない
やめてくださいよ
Please don't apologize.
Without you, I wouldn't even
have forced the tie.
こんな僕でも 監督のおかげで
同体にまで持ち込めたんです
悔いは ありません
I have no regrets.
あんなに後先考えず
やりきれたのも—
I was able to go in all guns blazing,
because Dachi High has the
strongest reserve member ever.
ダチ高には
最強のリザーバーがいるから
（蛍）ダチ高を頼みます　監督
Dachi High's fate is in your hands, Coach.
いや…
I mean...
桐仁
Kirihito.
Bout 22
"The Forgotten National Treasure, Onikiri Yasutsuna"
Sumo wrestlers have to be large and heavy.
（澤井）
相撲ってのは—
大きく
重くなきゃいけねえ
鬼丸(おにまる)や狩谷(かりや)のようなヤツらは
あくまで例外だ
Onimaru and Kariya are
exceptions to the rule.
無差別級だからって
誰でも出ていいわけじゃない
Just 'cause there are no weight categories
doesn't mean anyone can do it.
So which camp do you fall into?
お前は どっちだ？
スーパーヘビー級とも
渡り合える—
Are you an "exception to the rule"
that can take on a super-heavyweight?
一部の例外か？　それとも…
Or are you—
Hey.
（桐仁）おい
（澤井）うん？
せっかく 人が 久しぶりの
公式戦の空気に浸ってんだ
I'm soaking in the atmosphere of my
first official bout in a very long time.
その くせえ口 閉じてくれねえか？
Think you could stop flapping your gums?
（澤井）なっ…　アア…
（兵藤(ひょうどう)）ハハハハッ！
He's better at trash-talk than Sawai.
（兵藤）
口げんかじゃ 澤井の負けだな
（ダニエル）もう…
Aw, but Leon-chan's such a nice person.
理音(りおん)ちゃん ホントは優しいのに
ムリするからですよ
He should drop the bad guy act.
（四方田(よもだ)）
しかし あいつが出るとはな
I didn't expect to see him in the ring.
ウチに来たときは 土俵に
上がるそぶりは全くなかったが
He showed no indication of taking the ring
when he came to our school.
I wonder why they look so relaxed.
ヤツらの落ち着きようも気になる
Is Tsuji strong?
辻は強いのか？
If he is, why did they keep
putting Mitsuhashi in?
だったら
なぜ三ツ橋(みつはし)を使い続けた？
（小関(おぜき)）大丈夫だ
辻なら きっと やってくれる
It's fine. Tsuji will come through for us.
Even though he can only fight for 20 seconds,
たとえ 20秒しか戦えなくても
he's managed to throw both
Ushio and Master Shibakiyama.
潮(うしお)や柴木山(しばきやま)親方だって
投げたこともある
In those 20 seconds,
he's the strongest sumo around.
20秒間だけなら最強の力士だ
I've managed to remain out of the limelight
（桐仁）ここまで
隠し通すことができたのも—
because Mitsuhashi
managed to cling on till now.
三ツ橋が
準決勝まで粘ってくれたおかげだ
そもそも あいつが
背中を押してくれなかったら—
And if he hadn't encouraged me,
I would've given up on ever
standing in the ring again.
こうして土俵に上がることさえ
俺は諦めていたんだ
お前がくれた このチャンス
ムダにはしねえ！
I won't waste this chance you've given me!
Hands on the ground!
（審判）手をついて！
This guy...
（澤井）こいつ
スカした野郎かと思ったら…
He seemed like a smug dick at first glance,
なんだよ
暑苦しい目ぇするじゃねえか
but that look in his eyes
is seriously intense.
Right, let's see Onikiri in action.
（天王寺(てんのうじ)）
さあ お手並み拝見といこか 鬼切(おにきり)
（千鶴子(ちづこ)）ンッ…
（審判）はっきよい！
（澤井･桐仁）ンンッ！
Spirit!
He charged head-first at
a much bigger opponent?!
あの体格差で真っ正面かよ！
He's fast!
（澤井）速い！
（澤井）こいつ…
This guy...
Sorry, I don't have time to mess about.
（桐仁）悪いが 時間がねえ
ここで決める！
I'm going to end this now!
Push, Kirihito!
（火ノ丸(ひのまる)）押せ 桐仁！
（小関）いや…
No...
His grip's been altered.
芯をずらされてる
あれじゃ 押し切れない！
He can't push effectively!
クッ…　時間をムダにした！
I'm wasting time!
Try this on for size!
これなら どうだ！
チッ！　ダテに
栄(えい)大でレギュラー張ってねえな
He's not an Eiga High regular for nothing!
（澤井）
強(つえ)え！　とんでもない技のキレだ
He's strong!
His techniques are top notch.
一瞬でも気ぃ抜いたら やられる！
If he catches me off-guard, I'm done for!
I don't get it.
分からない
なんで あいつが控えなんだ？
Why is this guy only a reserve?
Maybe he's injured or something.
（兵藤）ケガでもしてんじゃね？
（四方田）ンンッ…
でも どこか焦ってるように見える
He does seem to be rushing for some reason.
In any case, I can't let him
grab the initiative.
（澤井）とにかく こいつの
ペースに つきあっちゃダメだ
フゥ…
（千比路(ちひろ)）マズイな
（小関）うん？
It's not looking good.
Sawai is smarter than he looks.
（千比路）あの澤井ってヤツ
思ったよりクレバーだぜ
The professor's at his best
when he's countering moves.
ハカセは
カウンターを得意とするタイプだ
逆に言えば 待たれると つらい
He struggles if his opponent
waits for him to come at them.
Just budging an opponent that size
（佑真(ゆうま)）
あれだけ重さのある相手を—
will take more strength
than Coach can muster.
自力で動かすだけの力が
監督にはねえ
If I stand still, I'm finished.
（桐仁）
止まったら終わりだ！　止まるな！
Don't stop! Move!
動け 動け！　時間がねえ！
Move! There's no time!
This is it.
やっぱり…
虫のいい話だったんだな
I was being too cocky.
Why did I think... a half-hearted
sumo wrestler who quit the sport...
俺みてえな
一度は相撲を捨てた半端者が—
could win anything at this level?
こんな大舞台でさ…
Kirihito!
桐仁！
（火ノ丸）お前は
そんなもんじゃねえだろう！
You've got more to give than that!
What are you waiting for?
どうした？
I've left myself wide open!
隙だらけだぜ！
Finally... you've decided to move.
（桐仁）やっと 動いたな
役に立ちてえんだ　俺も
I want to help the team, too.
一生のうちの たった１日
For just one day in my life...
For this one bout...
たったの一番くらい
超えてみせろ！
I'm going to push past...
（桐仁）限界を！
（澤井）ウッ…　ウオッ！
my limits!
Basic form: Three-point throw!
（桐仁）原型 三点投げ！
Basic
Form
Three-Point Throw
Basic
Form
Three-Point Throw
Basic
Form
Three-Point Throw
（３人）いけー！
Go!
（３人）わあ！
（千比路）…しっ！
（佑真）やった！
He did it!
No...
いや…
（ざわめき）
（四方田）フゥ…
（佑真）物言いだと！？
A protest?
The opponent's strength let him stay in it!
（小関）
パワーで強引に持ってかれた！
Hey, now...
おいおい　ハカセは もう限界だ
取り直しだけは勘弁だぜ
The professor's got nothing left.
Don't make him do a do-over.
Hey, are you okay?
（澤井）おい 大丈夫か？
（桐仁）ああ…　だ… 大丈夫
I-I'm fine.
（審判長）同体！　取り直し！
Simultaneous landings! Restart the bout!
No...
（蛍）そんな…
最高　ハァハァ…
Great...
Restarting the bout...
（蛍）
取り直しだなんて…
Hey...
（審判）おい 君　大丈夫か？
（桐仁）ハァハァハァ…
Are you okay?
ムリだ　棄権させよう！
He can't do it! He'll have to forfeit!
（小関）ウッ…
（千比路）決めるのはハカセ自身だ
That's for the professor to decide.
もっとも ホタルの手前—
But after what Hotaru did in his bout,
I can't see him backing out.
引き下がるなんて
できねえだろうがな
No, that's got nothing to do with it.
いや そういうんじゃねえな あれは
（火ノ丸）納得いかねえよな
That wasn't enough to satisfy you.
You haven't showcased
your style of sumo yet.
あんなのは お前の相撲じゃねえ
Your body's just getting warmed up.
ようやく
体も温(あった)まってきたところだよな
（桐仁）まさか もう１回
相撲を取っていいなんてな
I've been given another chance
to contest a sumo bout...
I'm grateful.
ありがてえ
みなぎるぜ
I'm ready to burst.
あっ 笑ってる
He's smiling?
He can't seem to get his
breathing under control.
一向に 息が整う気配がねえ
Just like our captain said,
he's got zero stamina.
主将の言うとおり
多分 異様にスタミナがねえんだ
組み止めて 長い相撲に持ち込めば
必ず勝てる
If I can grab him and
draw out the bout, I'll win!
Does he stand any chance of winning?
勝算あるのかよ…
In his current state, the prof only has
another five seconds in him at most.
今のハカセの状態じゃ
動けても せいぜい５秒
さっきみてえに時間を使われたら…
If the opponent wastes time like before...
（火ノ丸）体(たい)で劣るワシらの武器は
心と技じゃ
Our bodies leave us at a disadvantage,
so we rely on our techniques and spirit.
見せてやれ
Show them that.
何だよ？
What is this?
いるのか いねえのか分からねえ
その亡霊みてえな気配は
Is this guy really here or not?
His aura's like a ghost's!
Spirit!
はっきよい！
That was a weak charge!
当たりが弱(よえ)えよ！
Head Twist
Head Twist: Spiral Cut!
（桐仁）頭捻(ずぶね)り　渦切(うずきり)！
Spiral
Cut
（桐仁）ハァ…
ヘヘッ…　これよ これ
Yes... This is it...
There's no better feeling.
この瞬間が たまらねえんだ
Wow.
すげえ…
（アナウンス）
頭捻りで 東 辻君の勝ち！
Tsuji-kun, on the east side,
wins with a head twist.
Good work.
（火ノ丸）お疲れさん
ハァ…　ヘヘヘッ…
俺が ここまで してやったんだ
Look at what... you made me do.
If you lose after that, I'm coming after you.
（桐仁）負けたら許さねえぞ
（火ノ丸）おう
Gotcha.
Hey, who told you losing was an option?
（兵藤）…たく
負けてんじゃねえよ 澤井〜
After I gave us a head-start and all...
せっかく
俺が勢いつけてやったのによ
Yeah.
（澤井）ウッス…
You aren't hurt, are you, Leon-chan?
（ダニエル）
ケガは ないですか？　理音ちゃん
いい相撲でしたよ
That was some great sumo.
（四方田）相変わらず
バラバラだな ウチのチームは
Our team's as inconsistent as always.
ハァ…　うん？
Thanks, Mitsuhashi!
ありがとうよ　三ツ橋
（天王寺）かつて
千葉を騒がせた ふた振りの小学生
Two grade schoolers once
set Chiba alight with their sumo.
剛の鬼丸国綱(くにつな)と 柔の鬼切安綱(やすつな)
The hard Onimaru Kunitsuna,
and the soft Onikiri Yasutsuna.
なるほど
I see.
I'd heard he'd quit for a while,
一度は相撲を離れたらしいが—
but looks like he couldn't stay away
from the fun fest that is sumo wrestling.
こんな おもろいもん
やめられるわけないわな
（礼奈）な… なんで白楼(はくろう)が…
Wh-What's Hakuro doing here?
（天王寺）
ええ席は もう埋まってもうてな
ジャマするで
All the good seats were taken.
Sorry for invading your space.
I-Is your leg okay?
（首藤(しゅとう)）あ… 脚 大丈夫？
ごめんね ホント
I'm really sorry.
N-N-N-No, I'm sorry as well!
こちらこそ
いろいろと ホントに すみません！
Really sorry!
（千比路）ハハッ！　おい 五條(ごじょう)
（佑真）うん？
Hey, Gojo!
I can still see where your
little sister slapped you!
（千比路）背中に
くっきり残ってるぜ 妹の一撃
（佑真）あれは効いたな
That one sure resonated with me.
I'm all good now.
もう大丈夫だ
チームのために
きっちり働いてみせるぜ
I'm going to win this one for the team.
Yuma!
（火ノ丸）佑真
（佑真）うん？
相撲は好きか？
Do you love sumo?
これで最後じゃ
自分自身のために戦ってこい
This is your last bout.
Go do this for yourself.
Third bout.
（アナウンス）
中堅戦 東 五條君　西 四方田君
On the east side, Gojo-kun.
On the west side, Yomoda-kun.
（天王寺）四方田か…
Yomoda, huh?
（加納(かのう)）イヤな相手だな
（天王寺）ああ
He's a dangerous opponent.
Yeah.
He hasn't stood on the winners' podium
before, so he doesn't have a moniker,
（加納）表彰台には縁がなくて—
国宝の二つ名で
呼ばれることはなかったが—
but he always places highly
in individual tournaments.
個人戦では
いつも上位に名を連ねてる
（天王寺）せやねん！
You said it.
なのに あいつ 俺との３位決定戦で
手ぇ抜きよった！
But he held back against me when
I faced him in the third-place bout!
I was looking forward to that!
ちょっと楽しみやったのに！
Two national treasures are
heaping praise on him...
国宝２人が相手のことを褒めてる
He's a talented sumo wrestler
in peak condition,
そんな実力者で 体力も万全
なのに 佑真は
準決勝の激闘でボロボロ
while Yuma's still recovering
from his semifinal bout.
体重差も70キロ以上
And Yuma's giving away around 70 kilos.
どうやって勝てば…
How can he win this?
Yuma?
佑真？
Gojo, huh?
（四方田）五條か
まあ 大太刀(おおだち)の中では
当たりくじなほうだけど
Considering it's Dachi High we're facing,
it could've been worse,
but I need to watch out for his strikes.
さすがに
突き押しでは分が悪いか
Then again, if I get in
close and try to grab him,
…かといって
不用意に組みに行くと—
I might fall into a trap he's laid
for me, like Batbayar did.
バトバヤル戦のような
ワナがあるかもしれない
立ち合いは
ほぼ間違いなく諸手突(もろてづ)き
He's sure to start off with palm strikes.
なら 体重差を生かして
打たれながらでも前に出る！
I'll let him hit me and use my
weight advantage to force him back!
Spirit!
はっきよい！
Remember...
思い出せ　俺はダチ高の外で—
Outside of Dachi High...
I wanted to use this sport I love
俺がホレた この競技で—
何者かに なりたかったんだ！
to make something of myself!
（舟木(ふなき)）追い突き！
（西郷(さいごう)）まともに入った！
A lunge punch!
A solid hit!
（バトムンフ）
２人には分からないかもだけど…
You two might not know this, but...
His strikes really hurt.
あいつの突き 超痛いよ
Isn't he supposed to be running low on gas?
ガス欠じゃなかったのかよ！？
すごい連打です！
What a barrage...
四方田の巨体が浮いてきた！
Yomoda's body is leaning back!
Keep it up, Gojo!
いいぞ 五條！
Damn, this guy...
（四方田）くそ！　こいつ…
He always seemed to be
at the end of his rope,
いつも余裕がないイメージだったが
ここに来て—
なんで生き生きとしてんだよ！？
but on this big stage,
he's enjoying himself!
（蛍）いけー！
（礼奈）頑張れ 佑真！
Keep it up, Yuma!
Go!
You deserve credit for
seeking redemption.
（高荷(たかに)）
お前の贖罪(しょくざい)の気持ちは立派だよ
But that's not the only reason
you're here, is it?
でも それだけで
やってきたわけじゃないだろう？
仲間たちが真に お前に望むこと…
What your teammates want you
to do the most...
Yes.
そうだ　相撲に のめり込め！
They want you to engross yourself in sumo!
Yuma-san!
（３人）佑真さ〜ん！
You've got no room
behind you! Go sideways!
後ろないぞ！　横だ 横！
Use more of the ring!
土俵 広く使って！
五條さんは引き技に弱かった
だが それも過去の話！
Pulling techniques used
to catch Gojo-san out...
But that was then, and this is now!
（四方田）
やっぱ この距離はヤバイ
Staying at this distance is dangerous.
I have to grab his belt!
廻(まわ)しを…
Yomoda can't do a thing against him.
あの四方田が
何もさせてもらえないとは…
Partial Lunge: Castle Break Punch!
掛け追い突き 破城追掌(はじょうついしょう)！
Yes!
（礼奈）やった！
（２人）あっ…
やるやんけ
That sly fox.
He put distance between them to draw
an expansive strike out of him.
（天王寺）間合いを調整して
大振りの一発 掛け突きを誘った
（四方田）
ヘヘヘッ…　やっと捕まえたぜ
I've finally got you.
You think grabbing me ends it?
（佑真）組んだら終わり？
（四方田）あっ…
Not a chance.
（佑真）ざけんなよ
毎日 誰に
投げられてると思ってんだ！
Whose throws do you think
I have to deal with every day?!
I can feel his full weight when I grab him.
（佑真）組むと 改めて重(おめ)え
だが やるしかねえ！
But I've got to finish this!
Break!
（審判）待った！
Stay exactly where you are.
足の位置は そのままで
（四方田）ンンッ…
（礼奈）うわ…　すごい血
He's bleeding a lot.
A timeout to stop the bleeding.
（千鶴子）止血タイムですね
（蛍）少しでも休めるのは
ありがたいですけど…
It's good that he gets a chance to rest.
（佑真）すまん　大丈夫か？
（四方田）いやいや　こちらこそ
Sorry. Are you okay?
Oh no. It's fine, really.
（四方田）やっぱ強いね あんた
（佑真）うん？
You're pretty strong, aren't you?
（四方田）ふだんは あきれるほど
抜けてるヤツなんだけどな
Most of the time,
he's got more than a few screws loose.
But when he puts on his mawashi belt,
いざ 廻しを締めて現れると
稽古場の空気が変わる
the training area takes on a different feel.
Having him behind me puts me on edge.
あいつが後ろにいるってだけで
引き締まる
（狩谷）早く鬼丸と やりたくて
ウズウズしてんのか？
I guess he's impatient for
his bout against Onimaru.
いや 不器用な あいつなりの
激励なのかもな
Or maybe it's his awkward way
of offering encouragement.
Yuma!
（火ノ丸）佑真！
（佑真）うん？
Focus.
集中
Right.
おう！
（佑真）“強い”か
I'm strong, huh?
No, you're wrong.
いや 違(ちげ)え　強くなったんだ
I became strong.
ダチ高相撲部が
俺を強くしてくれたんだ
The Dachi High sumo club
has made me who I am.
I can't put this feeling into words.
この気持ちは
言葉じゃ伝えきれねえ
So...
だから…
Spirit!
（審判）はっきよい！
（佑真たち）ンンッ！
I'll win and make my gratitude tangible!
（佑真）
勝って 感謝を形にするんだ！
The tissues make it hard to breathe,
（四方田）詰め物のせいで 息が…
so I need to finish this now!
長引かせず ここで決める！
力比べじゃ かなわねえ
I can't overpower him, but...
だが 小関に教わった技—
Ozeki taught me a technique that'll help.
相手の右を殺し 重心を浮かす！
If I lift up my opponent's right arm,
it raises his center of gravity!
相手より重心が低ければ 押せる！
As long as my center of gravity
is lower than his...
I can push him!
This is my last high school sumo bout...
これが多分 高校最後の…
いや 俺の最後の相撲！
No, my last sumo bout ever!
Yomo!
（兵藤）ヨモ！
（澤井）ふんばれ！
Stand strong!
Yes!
（小関）よし！
（千比路）いけー！
Go!
今ここで 全て出し切れ！
I'll put everything on the line
right here, right now!
Overarm to underarm?
（加納）巻き替え！？
（バトムンフ）速い！
So fast!
（天王寺）ああいうとこやねん
（佑真）ウウッ…
This is what I'm talking about.
Looks like I really need to beef up.
俺も もっと体を大きくせなな
（天王寺）
腕力で浮かすんやない　腹でつる
He's not lifting with his arms.
It's all belly.
相撲の王道や
That's the traditional sumo way.
（四方田）
“スター選手の不在 外れ年”
A team without a star wrestler...
An off-year...
さんざん言われてきたけど
今は あいつがいる
A lot of people have disparaged us,
but now, we have him.
だからこそ
俺は団体戦に全てを懸けてきた
That's why I've staked it all
on the team tournament!
Winning here is what a captain does!
ここで勝ったら
主将っぽいっしょ！
（火ノ丸）暴れろ！　佑真！
Wriggle yourself free, Yuma!
もっとじゃ！　ガムシャラになれ！
Wriggle more! Like your life depends on it!
Strong...
強い…
He's strong and...
こんな強え男に 勝ちてえ！
I want to beat him!
Just like back then...
（佑真）あのときみてえに
もう一度 高鳴りてえ！
I want to set myself ablaze again!
（四方田）
相撲を始めて数か月でよ…
You've only been doing sumo for a few months.
If you ask me,
you're a prodigious talent yourself.
俺に言わせりゃ
あんたも十分 天才だよ
Yomoda-kun, on the west side,
wins by push down.
（アナウンス）
押し倒しで 西 四方田君の勝ち！
（四方田）フゥ…
If I hadn't saved my
strength coming into this,
（四方田）
個人戦で温存してなかったら
マジやばかったね
I would've been in real trouble.
佑真…
Yuma...
（舟木）佑真さん…
Yuma-san...
もう すっかり 力士だよな
He's become... a real sumo wrestler.
（橋(はし)）ああ
Yeah.
（佑真）
ハァハァ…　くそ！　ハァハァ…
Dammit!
（火ノ丸）どうじゃった？
（佑真）うん？
How was it?
Sumo's fun, isn't it?
相撲は楽しかったか？
I didn't really have time to enjoy it.
（佑真）
そんな余裕ねえっての　ハァ…
でも まあ…
But, you know...
It was fun!
楽しかったぜ
これで最後か…
So that was my last bout, huh?
フフッ…　勝ってりゃ
きれいに終われたんだけどな
Wish I could have gone out with a bang.
（佑真）ハァ…　ハァ…
こりゃ やめられねえかもな…
I'm not sure I can quit sumo after that.
相撲！
（加納）これで大太刀は２敗目
崖っぷちだな
That's Odachi's second loss.
They're teetering on the edge.
（天王寺）そのわりには
えらい落ち着いとるやないか
You wouldn't know it by
looking at them, though.
まだまだ分からんで この勝負
There's no telling who's
gonna win this match.
Odachi
High
School
Sumo
Club
（千鶴子）土俵は 女人禁制の
イメージがあるので緊張しますね
Women are forbidden from entering
the sumo ring, so I am a little nervous.
That only applies to pro bouts.
（礼奈）大相撲の話でしょう？
Plenty of girls do sumo
at the amateur level.
アマチュアには
女子相撲だってあるし
まあ マネージャーとして
相撲の理解を深めるためなら
I guess this will improve our understanding
of sumo and make us better managers.
Okay, here I come.
それじゃ いくわよ
はっきよい！
Spirit!
ウッ…　ウワッ！
Odachi
High
School
Sumo
Club
（礼奈）ダーッ！
（千鶴子）ハアーッ！
知識では堀(ほり)ちゃんが上
でも 運動神経なら負けない！
Hori-chan is more knowledgeable...
but I'm way more athletic!
Th-This is rather fun!
（千鶴子）た… 楽しいかも
H-Hey, wait!
あっ ちょ… 待って！
You're wide open!
（礼奈）隙あり！　ドリャー！
Winning Technique
Partial Throw
Winner
Reina
Winning Technique
Partial Throw
Winner
Reina
Winning Technique
Partial Throw
Winner
Reina
I'm sure I don't need to tell you what'll
happen if you breathe a word of this.
（礼奈）誰かに話したら
どうなるか分かってるわね？
Yes, ma'am.
（火ノ丸）はい　いや でも…
But, you know...
スカートの中 のぞかれたって
言い触らすから
Hori-chan will go around
telling everyone you peeked up her skirt!
堀ちゃんが！
Next Bout    "Spirit"
（火ノ丸）ええっ？
（千鶴子）私？
Me?!